National Negro Opera Company Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1934-1970, (193 folders) (Box 7-12)
  - Holmes, Alpha M. (National Supervisor and State Organizer, Kansas City, Missouri), 1940, 1942 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Holmes, Florence Allen, 1959 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Holmes, Luther, 1961 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Holt, Nora Douglas, 1955, 1962 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Homestead Messenger, Homestead, Pennsylvania. (Warren Fitzgerald, Editor), 1954 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Honduras. Embassy. (Celeo Davila, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Honory, Marvin, 1956, 1958 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Hood, Priscilla, undated (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hopkins, Nellie, 1961 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Horne, Lena, 1949, 1955, Two letters (carbon copies) written to Lena Horne. (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Horne Company, Joseph (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hoskins, John, Mr. and Mrs., 1960 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hot Shoppes, Inc. Executive Offices, Washington, D.C. (Edna MacQuarrie) 1959 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hotel Bellman Beneficial Association, Inc., 1951 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hotel Evans, Chicago (Stephen W. Mims), 1960 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hotel New Yorker, New York (G. C. Riss, Banquet Manager; Gene Voit, Manager), 1955 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hotel Theresa, New York, 1951, 1956 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hotze, Ed, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hovey, Serge, 1961 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Howard, Hugo and staff (Business Counsellors, Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Howard, James, 1944 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Howard, Perry, 1953 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Howard University. (Mordecai W. Johnson, President; Warner Lawson, Dean; William D. Allen, Head of the Music Department; W. Montague Cobb, School of Medicine, Department of Anatomy), 1937, 1949, 1958 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Hubert, Roberta Bosley, 1956 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Hueston, William C., 1944 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Huffman, Isaac O., 1958 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Hughes, Richard M., 1943 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Hunt, Roy, Mrs., 1944 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Hunter, S. Corinne, Miss, 1943 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Hurley Machine Company (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Hurok Attractions (Saul Hurok), New York, 1943, 1955, 1959 (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Hutchison, George H., 1936 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Hydrox Corporation, Chicago (E. E. Stewart), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Hylton, Taft H. (Simpson Methodist Church, Washington, D.C.), 1960 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Hymovitz, Edwin (Chatham Square Music School, New York), 1956 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Hynson, Millie, 1960 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Illery, Alma, 1954, 1958 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Illinois. Office of the Secretary of State. (Edward J. Barrett, Secretary of State), 1950 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Company (Chicago), 1944, 1952, The 1952 letter contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/25)
  - India. Embassy. (Mahomed-Ali C. Chagea, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Indonesia. Embassy. (Moekarto Notowidigdo, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Industrial Life Insurance Company (Philadelphia), undated, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Inland Steel Company (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Inniss, Josephine, 1941 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Insana, Silvio, 1944, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 9/26)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Local B-134 (Herman Washington), 1952 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - International Business Machine Company (IBM), New York (Wayne Watson), 1944 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - International Harvester Company (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (Washington, D.C.), 1948 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Iorus, Dorothy C., 1958 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Iran. Embassy. (Ali Gholi Ardalan, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Iraq. Embassy. (Moussa Al-Shabandar, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Israel. Embassy. (Abba Eban, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Italy. Embassy. (Manlio Brosio, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - J. Fischer & Brothers, undated (Box-folder 9/27)
  - Jackson, Charles E. (Real Estate, Pittsburgh), 1946 (Box-folder 9/28)
  - Jackson, Harrison S., 1949-1958 (Box-folder 9/29)
  - Jackson, Howard, 1958 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Jackson, Rev. J. H. (Olivet Baptist Church, Chicago), 1957 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Jackson, Lillian, 1952 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Jackson, Mrs. Marnette A., 1960 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Jackson, Nellie Carter (Grand Daughter Ruler, I.B.P.O.E. of the World, New York), 1955 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Jackson, Reginald, 1970 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Jaime, Benjamin Francisco, 1956, 1959 and undated see also Music: Jaime, Benjamin F. (Box-folder 9/31)
  - James, Ida Elaine, undated (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jamison, D. J., 1952 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jaretzki, Paul, 1956 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jefferson, Donald, 1954 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jeffries, Shirley, 1946 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jemmott, Hilda, 1957 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jenkins, C. F., 1937 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jenkins, Kate A., 1956 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jennings, Louise, 1960 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jet Magazine, Johnson Publications, Chicago (William Boone; Gerri Major, Society Editor), 1955, 1961 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Jewish Community Center of Greater Washington (Molly Jaffe), 1961 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johler, O. W., 1957 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - John B. Knignten, Jr. and Company (Chicago), 1952, 1957 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - John D. Page & Sons Milk Company (Pittsburgh), undated (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Alfred H., 1958 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Clyde, Mrs., 1962 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, D. Eugene, 1941, 1952 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Georgia Douglas, 1959 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Harriett, 1944 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Haywood, 1954 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Howard, 1961 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, J. Richmond, 1944 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Magga, 1961 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Johnson, Myrtle, 1944 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Johnson, N., 1954, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Johnson, Oliver E., 1961 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Johnson, Thomas O., 1944 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Johnson, Willie, Mrs., 1960 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Johnson Publishing Company, Chicago (John H. Johnson), 1955 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, Miss, undated (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, Antoinette, 1958 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, Burghardt D., 1961 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, C. S., 1957, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, Cynthia, 1956 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, Eva De Boe, 1935 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, George M., 1940 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, Harold, 1952 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, Helen R., 1961 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Jones, J. Wesley, 1936-1940, 1952-1959 (Box-folder 9/34)
  - Jones, Marian Page, 1961 (Box-folder 9/35)
  - Jones, William F., 1947, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 9/35)
  - Jones, William H. (Box-folder 9/35)
  - Joyce, Alberta L., 1952 (Box-folder 9/35)
  - Judimar School of Dance, Philadelphia (Marion C. Cuyjet, Maitresse d'Ballet), 1954, 1956 (Box-folder 9/36)
  - Julius Rosenwald Fund. (Dorothy Elvidge; Charles S. Johnson; H. S. McKeel; Margaret Utley; Fred G. Wale), 1943 (Box-folder 9/36)
  - Junior Century Club of Business and Professional Women, Inc., Washington, D.C. (Barbara Roy, President), 1960 (Box-folder 9/37)
  - Junior Police and Citizens Corps, Inc., Washington, D.C. (G. Howland Shaw, President, Board of Trustees), 1960 (Box-folder 9/37)
  - KDKA (Radio station: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania) (R. E. White, Program Director), 1954 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Kappels Jewelry Store (Pittsburgh), 1940 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Karlov, L., 1944 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Kaufman, Liliane, 1948 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Kaufmann's Department Store, Pittsburgh (Edgar J. Kaufmann), 1954 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Keene, Jesse, 1953 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Keller, Eloise, 1944 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Kelly, John P., 1944 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Kemp, Mr., 1952 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Kennedy, John F., Mrs. (Jacqueline Bouvier Kennedy), 1961, Letters written to Mrs. Kennedy. (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Keyes, Pansy, 1959, 1961 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Kimmey, Mrs. W. M., 1954 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - King, Juanita, 1957 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - King, Omega, 1948-1961 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Kinsman Optical Company (J. J. Jenkins, General Manager) 1954 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Kiser, Ruth, 1954 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Kitt Music Company, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), 1957 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Kraft Cheese Company, Chicago (J. L. Kraft), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Kraft Loans, Inc. (Al Kraft), 1950 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Kroger Company (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Kronheim, Melton S., 1952 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Kronheim, Milton S., 1959-1961 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Labor, Edward O., 1938 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lacey, Maggie, 1948, 1953 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Ladrey, Henry M., 1951 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lampkins, Daisy, 1943-1944, 1954 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lane, Frayser J., 1952 and undated (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Langsburgh's (Washington, D.C.), 1954 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lansburgh and Brother (Washington, D.C.), 1953 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lassiter, Mary, 1958, 1960 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lassiter, Vincent C., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Latney, Annie, 1960 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - La Tour, Lou, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Latvia. Legation. (Arnold Spekke), 1959 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Laundry Workers Joint Board of Greater New York, 1944, 1951 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Lauren-Waldon Associates, Inc., New York (Janet Lauren), 1954 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Lauterstein and Lauterstein (Counsel, Metropolitan Opera Association, New York), 1956 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lawless, T. K., 1957 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lawrence, George, undated (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lea, T. C., Mr. and Mrs., 1943 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lee, Alexander, 1954, 1958 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lee, Barbara Edwards, 1956-1957 see also Correspondence: Edwards, Barbara see also Notebooks: Assignments (B. Edwards) see also Notebooks: National Negro Opera Foundation (Notebook belonging to Barbara Edwards) see also Notebooks: Notes by Barbara Edwards see also Photographs: Lee Barbara Edwards (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lehmann, Otto A., 1944 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Leland, Mrs. (Mrs. Leland's Master Kitchens, Chicago), 1960 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lelong, Lucien (Mr. J. S. Stein), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 10/6)
  - LeMon, Lillian, 1936 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Leo Rose Clothiers (Chicago), 1953 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Letcher, Isadora A., 1958 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Levin, Joseph (Law Offices of Shinberg & Shinberg, Washington, D.C.), 1946 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Levinson Steel Company, Pittsburgh (Aaron, P. Levinson, President), 1954 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lewis, Emma, 1960 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lewis, Gladys Burton, 1960 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lewis, Gladys G., 1945 and undated (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lewis, Marion G., 1956 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lewis, Martha Smith, undated (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Lewis, Thelma M., 1958 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Liberia. Embassy. (George A. Padmore, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Licorish, David, 1951 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Light, David H., Mrs., 1954 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Lincoln Memorial Cemetery (Suitland, Maryland), 1959 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Lind, J. Allegria, 1944 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Lindsey, King, 1952, 1954 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Lipscomb, Joseph, 1960 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Little, George, 1954 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Lorance, Mehetabel, Mrs., 1959 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Lordly & Dame, Inc., Boston (Martin A. Forrest; Dana Lordly), 1956 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Lucas, James William, 1948, 1952, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Luce, Clara Booth, 1959 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Ludington, R. R., 1951, 1954 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Lustig, Ludwig (Artists' Representative, New York), 1944, 1952 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - M. E. Swing Company, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Mackley, Adelle, 1960 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Macklin, Jerene G., 1936, 1952, 1960 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Madison Square Garden, New York (Mr. Anderson), 1944 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Magruder's (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Main State Bank, Chicago (L. Shirley Tark, President), 1952, 1957 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Major, Thomas, 1951 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Malone, Annie M., 1943 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Mangrum, Alban T., 1944 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Manhattan Auto and Radio, Washington, D.C. (David Herson), 1952 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Manhattan Storage & Transfer Company, Washington, D.C. (Maurice Kressin, President), 1949 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Mansfield, Clarence, 1957 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Mansfield, Emmanuel, 1945 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - March, Ruth, 1954 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Marr, Warren, II, 1946, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Marshall, Hanna, 1961 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Marshall, C. Herbert, 1954, 1958 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Martin, Irene, 1960 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Martyn, Florence H., 1949 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Mary F. Handy Club (Mrs. A. V. Thornton, President), 1950 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Maxwelle, Joseph H., 1949 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - May, Marjorie Merriweather (Mrs. Herbert A. May), 1959 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - May-Beagle Concerts (Mr. Beagle), 1954 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Mayers, Wilnette K., 1958-1962 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Mayfield, Bethel Beersheba (Rhone), 1955-1956, 1961 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Mayle, B. H., 1941, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Mayo, J. H., 1961 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Mayo, Prisilla, 1952 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Mayo, Vera L., 1961 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - McAllister, Hazel, 1958 and undated (Box-folder 10/14)
  - McCleaves, Florence Cole Talbert, 1943 and undated (Box-folder 10/15)
  - McCune, Bob, 1961 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - McDaniel, Theresa B., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - McDonald, John, 1958 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - McDowell, Ellen C., 1945 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - McEnheimer, Marie, 1954 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - McFerrin, Robert, 1949, 1952, 1954 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - McGhee, Novella, 1945 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - McGowan, Mayoma, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - McNamara, Pat (U.S. Senator, Chairman, Public Works Committee, Washington, D.C.), 1958 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Mdodana, U. V., Mrs., 1944 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Meadow Gold Dairies, Inc. (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Means, Andrew, Mr. and Mrs., 1962 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Medas, Enyde, 1961 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Melart Jewelers (Washington, D.C.), 1952 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Mellor's Music Store, Pittsburgh (Mr. Baltz), 1941 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Menard, Edith, 1958 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Mendoza, Humberto, 1952 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Mercury Automobile Company (Pittsburgh office), 1954 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Meridian Hill Baptist Church (The Membership Club), 1960 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Mercer, Anne, 1958, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Merrill, J. J., 1944 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Merritt, Alice Haden, 1949 and undated (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Mesta, Pearl, 1959, 1961 and undated (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Metropolitan A.M.E. Church (Washington, D.C.), 1950-1961 and undated (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Metropolitan Brewers' Institute, New York (James G. Stanley, Administrator), 1944 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Metropolitan Funeral Home, Chicago (H. G. Hall, 1957 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Metropolitan Opera Association, Inc., New York), 1944, 1955-1956, 1959 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Metropolitan Police, Washington, D.C. (Robert J. Barrett, Superintendent), 1951 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Mexico. Embassy. (Don Manuel Tello, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Meyer, Agnes, 1959 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Meyer, Bryon (Tex & Jinx Program, NBC Building, New York), 1952 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Meyers, Irving, March 27, 1952, Contains list of the members of the chorus (dancers and singers) taking part in the March 29, 1952 presentation of Faust. (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Michaux, Elder Lightfoot, 1959 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Miles, Betty, 1958 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Miller, Gwendolyn A. M., 1959 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Miller, Hattye, Mrs., 1952 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Miller, Herbert T., 1955 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Miller, James, 1958 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Miller, Lynette, 1955 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Miller, Mabel, 1944 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Millstein, Reuben K., 1954, 1957 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Mines, P., Sr., 1951 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Mitchell, Doyle, 1948 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Mitchell, Juanita Jackson, 1958 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Monarch Wine Company, Inc., Brooklyn, New York, 1951 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Montgomery-Stubbs Motors, Inc. (Mr. Stubbs), 1951 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Moore, John W., 1936 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Moore, Margaret E., 1948 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morgan, Rose, 1957 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morganthau, Henry, III, 1955, 1958 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morocco. Embassy. (El-Mehdi Ben Aboud, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morris, Mary Rachael, 1954 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morris, Newbold, 1944 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morris, O. O., Mr., 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morrison, Mary C., undated (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morrison, Ruth, 1951 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morrissey, John, 1955 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Morton Salt Company, Chicago (Daniel Peterkm, Jr.), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Mosby, Louise, 1954, 1961 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Moseley, Margaret A. (District Grand Household of Ruth, No. 29, New Jersey), 1954, 1956 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Moses, Helen Carter, 1941 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Mothers of children who passed through the night (Minutes of meeting), March 8, 1960 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Mouzen, Olin T., 1943 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Murdoch, D. V., Mrs. (Chairman, Auditions Committee, Advisory Board of Directors, Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Murphy, Beatrice, 1958 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Murphy, John (Lowe Inc., New York), 1952 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Murphy, M., Mrs., 1960 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Murphy, C. T., 1952 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Musical Courier (Dorothy Bersin), 1944 and undated (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Myers, E. Pauline, 1960 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Myers, Mitchell (Law Offices of Myers, Hand & Walker, Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Nash, Joe, 1954 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - National Achievement Clubs, Inc., Pittsburgh Branch (Juanita Woods, secretary), 1948 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - National Association of Colored Women, Inc. (Irene McCoy Gaines, President), 1954, 1958 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - National Association of Colored Women's Clubs, Inc. (Beulah Carter, Headquarters Secretary, Washington, D.C.), 1953-1954, 1958, 1961 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - National Association of Negro Musicians, Inc., 1934-1940, 1949-1961 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - National Association of Negro Musicians, Inc. Pittsburgh Branch. (Howard H. Rodgers, Vice-President), 1935 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - National Bohemian Beer (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - National Brewing Company (Washington, D.C.), 1953 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - National Committee for Rural Schools, Inc. (New York), 1961 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - National Council of Negro Women, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), 1944, 1952-1960 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - National Maritime Union of America (New York), 1944 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Nauman, Henri, 1952 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Neely, Mabel L., 1960 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Nelson, Andrew D. (Chicago Negro Opera Guild), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Nelson, Fannetta, 1937 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Nelson, Gladys (Chicago Negro Opera Guild), 1945-1949 (Box-folder 10/29)
  - Nespoli, Uriel, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 10/30)
  - Neumann, J. L., 1943 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New, Luella C., 1944 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New England Conservatory, 1955 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New York Amsterdam News, (C. B. Powell, President/Editor; Betty Granger, Society Editor), 1955, 1958 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New York Enthusiast (Hans Hacker), 1956 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New York Guild (NNOC), 1955, 1957 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New York Post) (Leonard Lyons), 1951 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New York Telephone Company, 1956 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - New York Times (Pittsburgh Office), 1954 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Newman, Charles W. (Funeral Director, Chicago), undated (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Nicholls, Herbert S. (Washington, D.C. Guild, NNOC), 1944 and undated (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Nickerson, Camille, 1953-1961 (Box-folder 10/32)
  - Nine-Seventy-Five Optical Company (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Nitkins, Miriam, 1944 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Nixon, Richard M., Mrs., 1959, Consists of copies of letters sent to Mrs. Nixon. (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Norman, Johnnie Lu, Mrs., 1952 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - North Carolina Mutual Life Insurance Company (Pittsburgh Office), 1954 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - North Laundry (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - North Philadelphia Civic League, Philadelphia (Rev. Arthur E. Rankin), 1944 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Nurse, Godfrey, 1958 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Nyoka, Princess Consuelo, 1946, 1958 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - O'Brien, Miss (Board of Education, Brooklyn, New York), 1944 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - O'Loughlin, Roy, 1946-1949, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Oliver, Mrs. E. K., 1954 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Olson Rug Company, Chicago (W. E. Olson), 1952 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Opera House (Chicago). (Clayton Gilbert; J. Charles Gilbert, Managing Director), 1943, 1952, 1957 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Opera News. (Gerald Fitzgerald, Staff), 1956 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - O'Toole, Daisy, undated (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Otto McClarrin & Associates - Public Relations, Washington, D.C. (Otto McClarrin), 1959 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Overstreet, Geraldine, 1952 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - P. Lorillard Company (New York), 1951 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Padmore, Mrs., 1957 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Pakistan. Embassy. (Mohammed Ali, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Pan American Union, Washington, D.C. (Guillermo Espinosa, Chairman, Music Division), 1955 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Parker, Florence, 1951 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Parker, Henry, Mr. and Mrs., 1952 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Parker, Walter P. H., 1954 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Parris, Jean, Mrs., 1958 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Patrick, Thomas, 1952 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Patterson, Bessie, 1936 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Payne, George L., Rev. and Mrs. (Victory Baptist Church, Bronx, New York), 1956 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Payne, Jeannette M., undated (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Payne, Willard M., 1954, 1957, 1960 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Peacher, Millie, 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Pearson, Drew, 1959, 1961 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Peoples Currency Exchange (Chicago), 1952 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Peoples Drug Stores, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), 1953-1962 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Peoples First National Bank & Trust Company (Homestead, Pennsylvania), 1954 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peoples Gas & Coke Company (Chicago), 1952 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Pepsi Cola Bottling Company (Washington, D.C.), 1960 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Pernell, Charles, 1954 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Pernell, Ruth, 1954, 1958 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peru. Embassy. (Fernando Berckemeyer, Ambassador, and Mrs.), 1959 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peter Fox Brewing Company, Chicago (Frank Fox), 1952 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peters, Mr., 1944 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peters, Cortez, 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peterson, Caleb, 1955 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peterson, Cleon A., 1942 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Peyton, Alyce R., 1952 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Pharr, John B., Jr. (Law Offices of Bowman & Pharr, New York), 1952 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Pharr, Johnsie C., Mrs., 1945 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Phelps, Mande, undated (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer (Vlater H. Annenberg, Editor), 1954 (Box-folder 11/6)